Guide to the Lester R. Armstrong Photographs circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Snake Charmer: Pet parade, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1410)
- Snow fort, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1411)
- Snow sledding, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1414)
- Snow, McIntyre Pt., Circa 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1412)
- Snowman, 1945 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 1413)
- Snyder, Reva, 1953 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 1415)
- Solarized negatives: Experimental, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1328)
- Soldiers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1416)
- Spanish floral display, 1947 January 7 (Box 4, Folder 1417)
- Spider, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1418)
- Spider, 1953 September (Box 4, Folder 1419)
- Spinach harvesting: Ben Criscola place, 1947 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 1420)
- Spokane, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1421)
- Sports troller: Sea Hawk: Depoe Bay, Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1803)
- Stalker, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1422)
- Stamps, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1423)
- Stamps, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1424)
- Standard Oil Company: Dealer Conference: Marcus Whitman Hotel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Standard Oil: Conference: Walla Walla Hotel, 1946 December 5 (Box 4, Folder 1425)
- Standard Oil: Rea Ranch, 1946 April 24 (Box 4, Folder 1426)
- Stanley: Mrs. Betty: Baby, 1948 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 1427)
- Stanton, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1429)
- Stanton, Miss, 1946 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 1428)
- Star fish: Stevenson Washington: Westby, Joice, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1430)
- Starr, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1431)
- Starr, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1432)
- Starr, Burton, 1945 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 1433)
- Steamboat, Bill, Circa 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1434)
- Sterd, Sergeant Elmer D.: Squadron T1 Walla Walla Army air field, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1439)
- Stern, Marion: Alpha Phi:, 1948 April 16 (Box 4, Folder 1435)
- Sterns, Martin, 1946 October 4 (Box 4, Folder 1436)
- Stewart, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1437)
- Stouley: Waitsburg, baby and portrait, 1949 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 1438)
- Street Scene: Locust street, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1441)
- Street Scene: Locust street, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1442)
- Street scene: Smoke through trees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1440)
- Strike, Tel., Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1443)
- Struthers, Helen, 1948 March 19 (Box 4, Folder 1445)
- Struthers, Mrs. Harry L.: R.F.D, 1951 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 1444)
- Sturgeon: Pete's Sport Shop, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Sun Lakes State Park, Washington, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1804)
- Sunset: Columbia River Pasco, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1446)
- Sunset: Depoe Bay, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1447)
- Sunset: Depoe Bay, Oregon: Commercial Fishing Boat, August (Box 5, Folder 1794)
- Sunset: Long Beach, Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1448)
- Sunset: Olympic Peninsula, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1789)
- Sunset: Oregon Coast, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1808)
- Sunsets, 1947 July 5 (Box 4, Folder 1449)
- Sunsets, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1451)
- Sunsets: From Pasco Bridge, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1450)
- Sunsets: Olympic Peninsula: Kalaloch, Washington, August (Box 5, Folder 1793)
- Swallows, 1946 July 4 (Box 4, Folder 1452)
- Swartz, Sam: Furrier, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1453)
- Swimming, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1454)
- Tacoma, Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1455)
- Taft, Oregon: Fishing in surf, Circa 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1456)
- Tanks, oil, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1457)
- Taso, Mrs. A. O., 1951 July 3 (Box 4, Folder 1458)
- Taylor, Carpenter, 1945 August 16 (Box 4, Folder 1459)
- Taylor: Firebox: Libby McNeill: Libby, 43947 (Box 4, Folder 1460)
- Teague Motor Company Building, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Teague: Ford Motor Company, 1951 March 7 (Box 4, Folder 1461)
- Teal dog, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1462)
- Teasley, Geraldine, 1946 July 19 (Box 4, Folder 1463)
- Teasley, Miss, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1464)
- Telephone company, 1946 January 25 (Box 4, Folder 1465)
- Theatre, Little, 1948 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 1466)
- Theatre, roxy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1467)
- Thomas, 1948 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 1470)
- Thomas, Lowell, 1949 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 1469)
- Thompson, 1946 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 1471)
- Thompson, 1946 July 19 (Box 4, Folder 1472)
- Tire shop, camelback, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1473)
- Tollgate miscellaneous, couple and child, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1474)
- Tomlinson, Audrey, 1949 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 1475)
- Tomlinson, Bob, 1951 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 1477)
- Tomlinson, Bob: Family group, 1948 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 1476)
- Torkelson, Fire, 1950 January (Box 4, Folder 1478)
- Torkelson, Henry and Mrs., 1953 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 1479)
- Totem Pole: Lake Quinault, Washington, Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Tractor, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1480)
- Tractor, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1481)
- Trailer, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1486)
- Trailer, 1949 June (Box 4, Folder 1488)
- Trailer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1482)
- Trailer Camp, Bend Oregon, Circa 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1483)
- Trailer Park, Cannon Beach: Driftwood camp: Shipley, E.P., Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1485)
- Trailer: Nicholson, J. T., 1949 May (Box 4, Folder 1484)
- Trailer: Self, Circa 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1487)
- Traver, L.R., 1949 April 10 (Box 4, Folder 1489)
- Traver, L.R., Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1490)
- Trawler, Commercial: Close up: Port Angeles, Washington, Circa 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1814)
- Trawler, Commercial: Depoe Bay, Oregon, Circa 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1816)
- Tree: Advertising: College Place, Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1491)
- Tree: College Place advertising, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1492)
- Tree: Mill Creek, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1493)
- Tree: Sycamore, City Park, Circa 1944 (Box 4, Folder 1494)
- Trees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1495)
- Trees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1496)
- Trees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1497)
- Trees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1498)
- Trees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1502)
- Trees, poplar: Snake River, 1940 July (Box 4, Folder 1501)
- Trees, Whitman College, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1503)
- Trees: Blewett pass, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1500)
- Trees: Yakima Avenue, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1499)
- Trip, 1951 September (Box 4, Folder 1505)
- Trip: Hood Canal and Portland, 1953 July (Box 4, Folder 1504)
- Trough, Water: Clearwater, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1506)
- Tum-a-lum Lumber company, 1946 August 1 (Box 4, Folder 1507)
- Tum-a-lum Lumber Company, Main and 9th, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Tuna: La Push, Washington, Circa 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1815)
- Tunnel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1508)
- Turkey, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1509)
- Twin Sisters: Wallula Gap, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1799)
- Unidentified Group photograph], Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Union Pacific Old Timers Group: Lewis and Clark Park, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- United Bretheren Church Group, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- United Service Organizations, club, 1945 July 1 (Box 4, Folder 1515)
- [United Service Organizations, club: African American], 1944 October 8 (Box 4, Folder 1516)
- United Service Organizations Club: Alder street: Bingo game, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1514)
- United Service Organizations Club: Main street, 1945 July 1 (Box 4, Folder 1517)
- United Service Organizations, singles, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1518)
- United Service Organizations: Bell, M: Walla Walla Washington, Main street, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1513)
- United Services Organization: Walla Walla, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- United Services Organizations, 1945 November 27 (Box 4, Folder 1546)
- United Services Organizations Club: Main Street: General inside view, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1533)
- United Services Organizations: Alder Street: Halloween, Circa 1944 (Box 4, Folder 1532)
- United Services Organizations: Banquet, 1945 October 4 (Box 4, Folder 1547)
- United Services Organizations: Bennett, James: Two couples, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1545)
- United Services Organizations: Farewell party, 1946 June 24 (Box 4, Folder 1539)
- United Services Organizations: Halloween, Circa 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1534)
- United Services Organizations: Horn, Thomas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1538)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1535)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1543)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Barber Kelly, 1946 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 1540)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Halloween, Circa 1944 (Box 4, Folder 1537)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Langston Hughes, 1946 January 25 (Box 4, Folder 1550)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Linder, Doris, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1541)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Morris, Jerry: Four men, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1542)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Mrs. Babee, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1536)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Robinson, Hally: Thornton Brown: Group of four in settee, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1530)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Sewing class: Mrs. Bell and Mrs. Carmen W. Whitby, 1946 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 1549)
- United Services Organizations: Main Street: Two men, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1544)
- United Services Organizations: Occasion of Jubilee Singers, 1946 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 1551)
- United Services Organizations: Owens, Blanche: Group of three, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1528)
- United Services Organizations: Round up club dance, 1944 September 12 (Box 4, Folder 1552)
- United Services Organizations: Sewing class: Lieutenant Ermayne S. Faulke, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1548)
- Unknown [family portrait], Undated (Box 4, Folder 1531)
- Upholstering Shop: Furniture art, 1951 April 7 (Box 4, Folder 1510)
- Upton, Evelyn, 1949 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 1511)
- Utah Construction Company, 1950 March (Box 4, Folder 1554)
- Utah Construction Company: Traveling crane, 1950 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 1555)
- Vacation, Circa 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1557)
- Vacation: Craters of the Moon National Monument, Circa 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1556)
- Vacation: Glacier National Park, Circa 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1560)
- Vacation: Miscellaneous: Russel, Chris M, home, Circa 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1558)
- Vacation: Pictures personal, 1946 May (Box 4, Folder 1561)
- Vacation: Teton National Park, Circa 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1562)
- Vacation: Unprintable, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1559)
- Van Vranken, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1563)
- Vantage, Washington: Scenery, 1949 July (Box 4, Folder 1564)
- Varrattes: Weight lifter, 1946 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 1565)
- Vasalie, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1567)
- Vasalie, Betty, 1949 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 1568)
- Vasalie, Betty, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1570)
- Vasalie, Betty: Wedding, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1571)
- Vasalie: Wedding, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1572)
- Vases, France, 1950 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 1569)
- Vegetables, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1573)
- Veterans Affairs Hospital: Moving Chapel, 1947 March 13 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Veterans Hospital: Christmas picture, Circa 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1818)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars: Cooties, Circa 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1574)
- Victory Bond Drive: Walla Walla, Washington, 1942 October 17 (Box 4, Folder 1575)
- Victory Center, Circa 1957 (Box 4, Folder 1576)
- Victory Center: American Legion, Circa 1943 (Box 4, Folder 1577)
- Victory Center: Armistice, Circa 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1578)
- Victory Center: Crew of a bomber from overseas: Jack the Ripper, Circa 1943 (Box 4, Folder 1579)
- Victory loan, 1947 September (Box 5, Folder 1580)
- Victory night: VJ, 44060 (Box 4, Folder 1581)
- Victory Rally: Leslie, Joan: Adolf Menjo, Walter Pidgeon, Colvance, etcetera: Walla Walla Washington, 1942 September 5 (Box 4, Folder 1582)
- View: Mountain from Walla Walla County, 1944 February (Box 4, Folder 1584)
- View: Over Walla Walla Valley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1588)
- View: Panorama View of Walla Walla Valley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1585)
- View: Pikes peak, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1586)
- View: T.B. Hospital, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1587)
- View: The Cottonwood Canyon v., Copeland Ranch, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1583)
- View: Walla Walla Sanitarium, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1589)
- Views from Pikes Peak, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1590)
- Views from Pikes Peak, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1591)
- Vrattas: Weight lifter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1566)
- Wading boys, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1592)
- Wagner, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1593)
- Wagon emigrant: Meecham, Oregon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1594)
- Wagon jack, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1595)
- Wagon wheel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1772)
- Wagon Wheeler: Milton Pea Festival, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1598)
- Wagon Wheeler: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1596)
- Wagon Wheelers: Walla Walla Races, 1942 May (Box 4, Folder 1597)
- Wainwright, General, 1945 November 10 (Box 4, Folder 1599)
- Waitress, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1600)
- Waitress: Daughter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1601)
- Waitress: Scott and Catherine, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1602)
- Waitsburg: Scenery, 1950 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 1603)
- Walla Walla cabins: Mr. Fender, 1949 May (Box 4, Folder 1607)
- [Walla Walla County Fair: Fair and Frontier Days], Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Walla Walla Court: Interior and Exterior, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Walla Walla Draper Company, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1608)
- Walla Walla Fair, 1947-1949 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Walla Walla Fair: Wheeler Dinner: Clodius, Richard, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 321)
- Walla Walla from Marcus Whitman, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1605)
- Walla Walla from Walla Walla Grain Growers Elevator, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1606)
- Walla Walla Grain Growers, 1947 August 23 (Box 4, Folder 1609)
- Walla Walla Grain Growers, 1948 August 23 (Box 4, Folder 1610)
- Walla Walla Grain Growers: Elevators, 1947 August (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Walla Walla High School: Rally Wenatchee, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Walla Walla Lodge, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1611)
- Walla Walla Scenes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1604)
- Wallace, Myrtle, 1948 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 1612)
- Wallula, 1952 December (Box 4, Folder 1613)
- Wallula, Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1614)
- Wallula, 1952 June (Box 4, Folder 1615)
- Wallula, 1952 July 20 (Box 4, Folder 1619)
- Wallula, Washington: East side of Wallula Gap, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Wallula Gap and Columbia River, 1953 December (Box 4, Folder 1621)
- Wallula Gap, Rock Structure, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Wallula: Beach resort: Twin sisters rocks, 1952 August 3 (Box 4, Folder 1618)
- Wallula: Railroad tracks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1616)
- Wallula: Railroad yards, Circa 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1620)
- Wallula: View from Walla Walla River, 44025 (Box 4, Folder 1617)
- Walters, Patty, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1622)
- Wanda, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1623)
- Water tank, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1626)
- Waterwheel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1627)
- Waves: Ocean, Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1628)
- Weaver, General, 1949 February 6 (Box 4, Folder 1629)
- Webber, Mrs. N. T.: Child of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1630)
- Wedding: Mr. and Mrs. Robert Clegg, 1946 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 1634)
- Wedding: Mr. and Mrs. Robert Clegg, 1946 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 1635)
- Wedding Anniversary: Mr. and Mrs. D. G. Keyes, 1946 July 7 (Box 4, Folder 1632)
- Wedding Hastings: Wedding Breakfast: Grand Hotel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1641)
- Wedding party: Potter, 1945 March (Box 4, Folder 1245)
- Wedding, Lowden, 1945 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 1644)
- Wedding, Lowden, 1946 April 21 (Box 4, Folder 1645)
- Wedding: Bean, 1946 February 6 (Box 4, Folder 1633)
- Wedding: Cunnington 611 military, 1946 October 20 (Box 4, Folder 1636)
- Wedding: Dagget, 1946 April 21 (Box 4, Folder 1637)
- Wedding: Erwin, 1949 February 6 (Box 4, Folder 1638)
- Wedding: Evonder, 1949 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 1653)
- Wedding: Fink: Emanuel Lutheran Church, 1947 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 1639)
- Wedding: Hutton, 1945 August 19 (Box 4, Folder 1642)
- Wedding: Jilg, 1946 November 3 (Box 4, Folder 1643)
- Wedding: Maddox, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1646)
- Wedding: Maddox, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1647)
- Wedding: Maddox, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1648)
- Wedding: Maddox, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1649)
- Wedding: McCaw Hospital, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1650)
- Wedding: Meiner and Torretta: St Francis Church: Walla Walla Washington, 1946 November 28 (Box 5, Folder 1660)
- Wedding: Meiner and Torretta: St. Francis Church: Walla Walla, Washington, 1946 November 28 (Box 5, Folder 1659)
- Wedding: Mr. and Mrs. Vern Alexander: Prescott, 1946 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 1631)
- Wedding: Munns and Oliver, 1947 November 11 (Box 5, Folder 1651)
- Wedding: Payne: Tom Payne, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1652)
- Wedding: Schabaz, L.T., 1946 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 1654)
- Wedding: Shaw, 1945 June (Box 5, Folder 1655)
- Wedding: Spear and Mackie, 1947 September 7 (Box 5, Folder 1656)
- Wedding: Starr, 1947 January 12 (Box 5, Folder 1657)
- Wedding: Starr, 1946 September (Box 5, Folder 1658)
- Wedding: Steinhardt, Otto, 1946 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 1640)
- Wedding: Wedemeyer, 1945 November 23 (Box 5, Folder 1661)
- Weddings: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Welder, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1662)
- Weller, Jackie, 1950 June 14 (Box 5, Folder 1663)
- Wenatchee valley, 1940 July (Box 5, Folder 1664)
- West, Herb: Hat throw, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1665)
- West, Herbert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1666)
- West, Herbert: Milking contest, 1947 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 1667)
- West, Herbert: Whitman Monument, Circa 1943 (Box 5, Folder 1668)
- West, Mayor Herbert and wife: Eagles Banquet, 1946 January 7 (Box 5, Folder 1669)
- Westport, Washington, Circa 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1670)
- Wharf Fisherman's, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1671)
- Wharf Fisherman's: Newport, Washington, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1672)
- Wharf: Small boat: Port Angeles, Washington, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1673)
- Wharf: Sports: Depoe Bay, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1674)
- Wheat, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1675)
- Wheat, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1676)
- Wheat Elevator: Port Kelley, Undated (Box 2, Folder 461)
- Wheat elevators, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1677)
- Wheat harvest, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1678)
- White Pass, Washington, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- White, Harold: Funeral, 1947 July 7 (Box 5, Folder 1681)
- White, Harold: Funeral, Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Whitehead and Bingham, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1682)
- Whitehead and Bingham, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1683)
- Whitehead and Pope, 1947 April 18 (Box 5, Folder 1685)
- Whitehead, Janet, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1684)
- Whites Nursery, 1949 September (Box 5, Folder 1686)
- Whitman annual: Whitman College, 1946 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 1699)
- Whitman College Lab charts: Pope, Circa 1947 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- [Whitman College: Alpha Chi], Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Whitman College: Alpha Chi Omega dance: Odd fellows dance, 1946 November 16 (Box 5, Folder 1692)
- [Whitman College: Alpha Chi Omega Dances], Circa 1947 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Whitman College: Annual, 1946 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 1700)
- Whitman College: Annual, 1940 May 3 (Box 5, Folder 1701)
- Whitman College: Annual pictures, Circa 1946 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Whitman College: Beta Theta Pi, Circa 1947 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Whitman College: Delta Delta Delta], Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
- [Whitman College: Kappa Kappa Gamma], Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Whitman dance: Alpha Chi Omega, 1947 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 1689)
- Whitman dance: Alpha Chi Omega, 1947 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 1690)
- Whitman dance: Alpha Phi Omega, 1947 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 1694)
- Whitman National Monument Dedication, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Whitman: Alpha Chi Omega, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1687)
- Whitman: Alpha Chi Omega dance: Pledge dance M.W., 1949 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 1693)
- Whitman: Alpha Chi Omega: Dance: Miss Anderson, 1948 May 21 (Box 5, Folder 1688)
- Whitman: Alpha Chi Omega: Lincoln day dance: Phillis Schultz, 1948 February 12 (Box 5, Folder 1691)
- Whitman: Alpha Phi dance: Marcus Whitman, 1948 November 19 (Box 5, Folder 1698)
- Whitman: Alpha Phi group: Miss Marion Stern, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1695)
- Whitman: Alpha Phi: Amery residence, 1947 May 25 (Box 5, Folder 1697)
- Whitman: Alpha Phi: Marion Stern, 1949 March 5 (Box 5, Folder 1696)
- Whitman: Athletic meet, 1949 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 1702)
- Whitman: Beta Halloween Party, 1948 October 30 (Box 5, Folder 1703)
- Whitman: Beta House party, 1948 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 1706)
- Whitman: Beta House: Beta pledge party, 1949 September 30 (Box 5, Folder 1707)
- Whitman: Beta House: Candidate for president, 1948 April 27 (Box 5, Folder 1704)
- Whitman: Beta House: Homecoming parade, Circa 1948 (Box 5, Folder 1705)
- Whitman: Beta Pledge dance, formal: Grand Hotel, 1948 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 1709)
- Whitman: Beta Theta Phi, 1947 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 1711)
- Whitman: Beta Theta Phi, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1712)
- Whitman: Beta Theta Phi banquet, 1947 November 15 (Box 5, Folder 1708)
- Whitman: Beta Theta Phi: Dance party: Beta House, 1947 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 1710)
- Whitman: Bingham, Lois, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1713)
- Whitman: Boating: Lakum Duckum, 1949 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 1715)
- Whitman: College dance: Delta Gamma, Grand Hotel, 1947 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 1718)
- Whitman: College dance: Pi Mu, 44179 (Box 5, Folder 1732)
- Whitman: College sorority group, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1716)
- Whitman: College winter view, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1717)
- Whitman: College: Painting Memorial Hall, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1719)
- Whitman: Dance: Pi Mu, 1947 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 1733)
- Whitman: Garrison Phillis: Alpha Phi, 1947 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 1720)
- Whitman: Girls Trio: At Alpha Chi Pledge party, 1949 December 12 (Box 5, Folder 1721)
- Whitman: Homecoming parade, 1947 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 1722)
- Whitman: Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1949 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 1723)
- Whitman: Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1948 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 1728)
- Whitman: Kappa Kappa Gamma dance: Grand Hotel: Mary Harvey: Miss Polly, 1948 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 1724)
- Whitman: Kappa Kappa Gamma pledge dance: Marcus Whitman, 1947 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 1726)
- Whitman: Kappa Kappa Gamma: Marcus Whitman: Nancy McKay, 1949 November 11 (Box 5, Folder 1725)
- Whitman: Kappa Kappa Gamma: Pre-vacation group, 1948 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 1727)
- Whitman: Navy plaque award, 1947 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 1729)
- Whitman: New president: student: Reid, Pete: Jim Boule, Cliff Harrison, 1949 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 1730)
- Whitman: Phi Mu formal: Pledge dance: Marcus Whitman, 1949 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 1734)
- Whitman: Phi Mu pledge dance: Little Theatre, 1949 November 12 (Box 5, Folder 1737)
- Whitman: Phi Mu: Group shots: Thomas, Margaret, 1949 May 19 (Box 5, Folder 1735)
- Whitman: Pi Mu journal: Formal dance: Marcus Whitman: Anderson, Miss: Mary Harvey, 1948 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 1736)
- Whitman: Pi Mu: Group shot: Miss Anderson, 1948 March 8 (Box 5, Folder 1731)
- Whitman: Play: Blythe spirit, Circa 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1714)
- Whitman: Tri Delta float: Homecoming: Building float, 1949 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 1738)
- Whitman: Tri Delta: Delta Delta Delta: Formal American Legion Hall: Hawes, Carol, 1949 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 1739)
- Wilkins, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1740)
- Williams, L. D. (Dutch): Fuel truck, 1950 August 11 (Box 5, Folder 1741)
- Williams, Willie, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1553)
- Wilson, 1946 November 18 (Box 5, Folder 1743)
- Wilson boy, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1742)
- Wilson, Mrs. Charles and boys, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1745)
- Wilson, Mrs. Charles: Two boys wearing Buck Rogers suits, 1950 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 1744)
- Wilson, Spud, 1944 May (Box 5, Folder 1747)
- Wilson: Spokane, Washington, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1746)
- Wilson: Standard Oil: Overseas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1748)
- Windstorm: Walla Walla, 1950 November (Box 5, Folder 1749)
- Windstorm: Walla Walla, Washington, 1950 November (Box 5, Folder 1773)
- Winkler: Harvesting: Moore, Luther, Circa 1942 (Box 5, Folder 1750)
- Winton, Ned, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1751)
- Wiseman, Chas [Charles]: Service station burning, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 25)